https://www.bruceclay.com/privacy/

CALL US (866) 517-1900
Search for:
Search Marketing > Our Commitment To Privacy
Our Commitment To Privacy
This Privacy Statement is effective as of May 2018.
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available in our global footer navigation and from pages where personally identifiable information may be requested.
The Information We Collect
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Bruce Clay, Inc. website and data we may collect through off-site channels such as Facebook. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages may include:
Name
Address
Email address
Phone number
Additional info appropriate to projects being managed or serviced by Bruce Clay, Inc. or international region offices
When purchasing something through our website such as a tools subscription, training registration or software product, the following information may also be collected:
Credit/debit card information
Billing name and address, for credit/debit card verification
The Way We Use Information
We use the information you provide about yourself for various purposes, such as the following:
Access and use of websites or other online services
We record information necessary to provide you with access, for the operation of the website and for us to comply with security and legal requirements in relation to operating our site, such as passwords, IP address and browser settings. We also collect information about your activities during your visit in order to personalize your website experience, such as recording your preferences and settings, and statistics to help us improve and further develop our websites, products and services.
Fulfilling your request for information, support, or order
When you place an order or submit a request, we use your information only to fulfill that order or request. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. For example, we use information provided that is descriptive of a website as project data unique to that website. We use return email addresses to answer the requests we receive and to provide reasonable notification of our project, service, or product news and updates. Most email addresses we receive are used to provide a free subscription to our blog. Such addresses are not shared with outside parties beyond the third-party services such as email service provider(s) that we use to fulfill these requests.
A secure third-party billing service is used to maintain credit/debit card information and process any recurring payments, such as a monthly tools subscription.
Marketing
Most information we collect about you comes from our direct interactions with you. When you register for a training course, for example, we collect information (online or offline) needed to process your registration, and during an event we may collect information from your participation in surveys. We combine the personal information we collect to develop aggregate analysis and business intelligence for conducting our business and for marketing purposes. You can choose to receive information by email, telephone or postal mail about our products and services, or sign up for a blog subscription or to receive news and updates.
We use analytics, including non-identifying and aggregate information, to better design our websites, products and services. Where we reference use of your personal information in relation to marketing or development of our websites, products or services, we do this on the basis of our or a third party’s legitimate interests, or with your consent.
Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above.
Our Commitment To Data Security
We intend to protect your personal information and to maintain its accuracy. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate and reasonable physical, administrative and technical procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. We also require that our third-party suppliers protect such information from unauthorized access, use and disclosure.
Our Commitment To Children’s Privacy
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 16, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 16.
How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information
You can request to access, update, correct or delete your personally identifiable information. You also have the right to object to direct marketing.
Tools subscribers can access their information by logging in to the SEOToolSet and visiting the update page appropriate to that information. NOTE: Login is mandatory. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.
You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error.
To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.
You may have additional rights pursuant to your local law applicable to the processing.
How To Contact Us
Should you have questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please contact our data protection officer by email to dpo@bruceclay.com or call us at 1-805-517-1900 and ask to speak to our data protection officer.
For the purposes of the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), the controller of your personal information is Bruce Clay, Inc., 2245 First Street, Simi Valley, California 93065, United States.
Search Engine Optimization Guide
PPC Guide
Paid Social Guide
Free Executives Guide for SEO
SEO for Dummies
Content Marketing Guide
SEO Agency
PPC Agency
Serving North America based in the Los Angeles Metropolitan Area
Bruce Clay, Inc. | 2245 First St., Suite 101 | Simi Valley, CA 93065
Voice: 1-805-517-1900 | Toll Free: 1-866-517-1900 | Fax: 1-805-517-1919
SEO SERVICES
SEM/PPC
CONTENT
SOCIAL MEDIA
SEO TRAINING
SEO GUIDE
SEO TOOLS
TECHNICAL SEO
CONTACT FORM
×
This site is protected by reCAPTCHA and the Google Privacy Policy and Terms of Service apply.
INQUIRE NOW
About Us
Privacy
Ethics
Sitemap
Copyright © 1996 to 2020 Bruce Clay, Inc. All rights reserved.
We use cookies to offer you a better site experience and to analyze site traffic. Read about how we use cookies in our Privacy Policy. If you continue to use this site, you consent to our use of cookies.
Got it
